http://www.efcanet.org/privacy-policy

Home
Privacy policy
Privacy policy
EFCA is an international non-profit association and governed by title III of the law of 27 June, 1921 on non-profit associations, foundations and international non-profit associations.
What data do we collect?
EFCA collects the following data:
- Personal identification information (name, email address, phone number, etc.)
- EFCA does not use cookies.
How do we collect your data?
You directly provide EFCA with most of the data we collect. We collect data and process data when you:
- Register online for any of our services.
- Voluntarily complete a customer survey or provide feedback on any of our message boards or via email.
- Use or view our website via your browser's cookies.
How will we use your data?
EFCA collects your data so that we can:
- Manage your account.
- Register you for events.
How do we store your data?
EFCA securely stores your data.
EFCA will keep your contact details until you unsubscribe.
What are your data protection rights?
EFCA would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:
- The right to access: you have the right to request EFCA for copies of your personal data.
- The right to rectification: you have the right to request that EFCA corrects any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request EFCA to complete information you believe is incomplete.
- The right to erasure: you have the right to request that EFCA erases your personal data.
- The right to restrict processing: you have the right to request that EFCA restricts the processing of your personal data.
- The right to object to processing: you have the right to object to EFCA's processing of your personal data.
- The right to data portability: you have the right to request that EFCA transfers the data that we have collected to another organisation, or to you directly.
If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at our email: efca@efca.be.
Privacy policies of other websites
The EFCA website contains links to other websites. Our privacy policy applies only to our website, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their privacy policy.
Changes to our privacy policy
EFCA keeps its privacy policy under regular review and places any updates on the web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 21 June 2019.
How to contact us
If you have any questions about EFCA's privacy policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to contact us by email (efca@efca.be).
How to contact the appropriate authority
Should you wish to report a complaint or if you feel that EFCA has not addressed your concern in a satisfactory manner, you may contact the Information Commissioner's Office.
